Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
Then, thus, a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting?
Either way, I'm feeling alive!
Look out below!
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
Raise your flag up high!
Hail a brand new dawn!
Blaze across the sky!
Time to journey on!
On your mark!
Come aboard with me!
We're on Earth, a legendary! Hooray!
If you can show your breath!
Then we'll make some waves!
We're all not daunted!
Ain't no beginners!
Cause if you're wanted!
Then you're a winner!
For we are on the cruise!
And freedom is the only rule!
Fearless night and day!
Cause that's just our way!
Find one piece!
I'll be the first!
I'll put it be so bad!
I could burst!
It's all this real!
It must be cause my hand's on the wheel!
I'm done playing, filled with the waiting!
In a world I'm feeling
alive, but I'll be loud!
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We have come so far!
Gotta make it to the end!
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind!
I've always got your back, my friend!
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward!
Dreaming from the very
first day, I'd make my name!
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed!
I'm done playing through,
it's a wave in the air!
The world I'm feeling
alive, look out below!
Wake up, sunshine!
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We go!
Brother, it's too hard to dig here!
Of course it is!
This island is all rocks and tree roots!
No, don't bury us!
We're victims too!
Please, I'll do anything you want!
Just let me live!
Captain Luffy!
No, I mean Black!
He made us do this!
Listen, I have a secret to share with you!
We didn't give a damn about going to
the new world with the Straw Hats!
The reason we joined!
Was so we could stab them
in the back and collect
their bounties without them
ever suspecting a thing!
No! Drift! Stop it!
I don't know what that goofy stuff is,
but you're gonna kill
him if you keep that up!
I will let my friend die!
Uh-oh.
That's weird.
And sure,
your Straw Hat did look a little off,
but it had been two years,
so I didn't think much of it.
You lied without remorse,
and deception is a sin.
One that you will be buried for.
Brother, how goes the grave?
I'm digging! I'm digging!
Sinners all, these poor fools.
Gods in heaven.
Please, forgive them.
Grant them peace and death.
Peace, yes, but not death.
Still, it's not all bad, I suppose.
I did find the real Luffy.
I told you there wasn't
any choice in the matter.
What did you expect?
Dark King Rayleigh was there.
He's as strong as Kizalu.
Even with the pacifistas, we
couldn't so much as slow him down.
Unfortunately, the Caribou Brothers
escaped along with the rest of their crew.
It seems they took some of the
fake Straw Hats with them as well,
though I can't imagine why.
At any rate, we captured
most of the pirates,
even though the real Straw Hats
heavily damaged two of our pacifistas.
One of the units was the same
prototype they fought before.
Its strength hasn't changed in the
last two years that's bad news for us!
I don't know what they've
been up to but the straw
hats are immeasurably more
dangerous than before!
Tell the Marines in the new world that
they have a new threat coming their way!
The Straw Hats have returned and they're
stronger than we could have imagined!
A pity they had
to take off so
soon but But I'm proud
of them. They're tough.
They're gonna do just fine.
You were watching?
Yes, I'm a big fan.
I know that smile, Ray.
What's on your mind?
Huh?
It's nothing, Rayleigh.
Hey, that's a nice ship you got there!
Thanks, but it's not exactly mine.
Rather, I stole it after
my house burned down.
Oh, yeah?
And what's your name?
Rayleigh.
My name's Roger.
It's destiny meeting you.
I say, how about we team up and
turn this whole world upside down?
Huh?
And I thought I drank too much.
I don't know who you are or what
you're selling, but I'm not interested.
Before then, I never
believed much in fate.
But maybe nothing really
happens by accident.
We're just too blind to see all the signs.
Anyway, that hat found the right man.
So long as it sails,
I'll stay here, waiting.
Because I want to see a
new king before I die.
The surface is already
so far away. What a view!
I've been under before.
The portholes on a submarine?
They got nothing on this!
We're sinking! Sinking!
What if we get a leak?
This is freaking me out!
Yeah, it feels like we're
leaving the whole world behind.
It's eerie no big deal I've done this
like a bajillion times before it's cool.
The ocean sure is
awesome look at that they
really are trees
they're giant mangroves.
You can't tell when you're up top but
it's sure quite a sight to see from down.
Here the majesty of nature
is truly humbling who
cares I've seen this cuz You
got on the wrong ship! Shut up!
Don't ruin this for us!
These roots, they're beautiful.
And think about it.
They stretch all the way down
to the bottom of the sea.
Okay, you win.
Hey, Chopper, I think there's
something behind that tree.
Whoa!
It's huge!
It took us long enough to get here.
But whatever, it was worth the wait.
I wonder what comes next.
Oh, fishies!
And then I can grab them!
I see.
These look pretty good, too.
Here goes.
That's not funny!
If you put that bubble in we'll
die, I'm gonna kill you! Twice!
Nami, you know how the
coding works, right?
Can we get some basic tips before
another idiot flips out on us?
Good point. Okay.
Rayleigh gave me a manual,
but I can summarize it.
So, listen closely, okay?
It's real!
I could die happy!
Saatchi!
You don't have to take us with you!
Oh, slip it out now, idiot!
What?!
His nosebleed shot him out! Saatchi!
Get out of the ocean!
Bright sea water! Dammit! Keep pulling!
Sanji, what the heck
happened to you back there?
I knew you were weak to pretty
girls, but this is a real liability.
You're supposed to be cool.
That poor man.
I can only imagine the horrors he must
have endured during the past two years.
Let's hope he lives long enough to see
the mermaids he was so looking forward to.
And let's also hope they aren't quite so
lovely that the sight of
them strikes him dead.
When we get there, we'll have
to ask for blood donations.
But they won't be human.
So,
Sunny's coding has the same
properties as the bubbles on Sabaody,
meaning that objects or people can pass in
and out without causing
it any harm at all.
Spare me the bubble science!
We got a man down here!
Sanji aside, she's not wrong.
We saw this all over Sabaody.
It only stretches so far, then
allows an object to pass through.
So the good news is if
we get attacked by any
nasty sea creatures we
can still fire cannons
at them just like we
would if we were above
water wait so what would pop it is it that
durable it does fine
with single objects but
if too many things pass
through at once then
it'll break let's see like if the sea king
clamps down on the ship
for example that's bad
Also the coating doesn't
protect the ship from
anything except water so
if we crash into a rock
or a trench and the
mass breaks or something
like that then the bubble
could also burst so it's
not like we can just
bounce around down here
still as long as we take
the usual precautions we
should be fine i mean i'm
sure luffy will try to
get us all killed but what
else is new so we're in
the clear after all good
well in theory at least
but a lot of ships try
to make the trip to fish
man island and over 70
percent of them sink we
are so dead one Gum-Gum
gatling and i bet i can
catch all the fish swimming
out there yeah if i
couldn't have holes in
this bubble thing i bet i
could catch even more
weren't you listening to
nami that's too many holes
our chances down here?
are bad enough as it is!
Oh, break your bones!
Let's fix them!
Let's break them again! No fair!
Haji said he'd show us the Fishman Island?
Like it was no big deal, And now
we're stuck in this death bubble!
slowly descending to our demise! Oh, yeah!
Lunchtime!
They packed a bunch of food for me!
Since Sanji's sick, we should
have ourselves a Pikmin!
Yay!
All that screaming made me hungry!
And I'm wasting away! Cool.
We don't have to stir it or
anything right now, do we?
Nope.
We'll just be cruising on the sea
current till we get further down.
But there's something you guys should
probably know before we reach Fishman Island.
It's robot stuff, right?
Sorry, no new secrets.
Secrets inaccessible, Robo.
He speaks robot!
Like Usopp said,
Hachi was supposed to show us the
way to Fishman Island himself,
but he got hurt real bad back on Sabo Odi.
He came down here ahead of
us to get medical treatment.
Anyway, it was the same
thing that happened to Devil.
Meaning, he was protecting the
Sunny from anyone who came for it.
Things got ugly about a year ago when the
Navy found out the ship was docked there.
Both him and Devil got
taken out in a big fight.
Huh?
Wait, a year?
Then who was protecting
the Sunny after that?
We had one more secret ally.
Someone who separated us two
years ago, for better or worse.
The Warlord.
Turns out Bartholomew Kuma was
on our side the whole time.
A few days back.
When I made it to the Sunny,
I couldn't believe my eyes.
He was right there.
I've been waiting for you.
What the hell are you doing here?
Mission accomplished.
You saw for yourself.
There wasn't a single
scratch on the Sunny.
Later, Rayleigh gave me the whole story.
I am a member of the Revolutionary Army.
If it's within my power, I want to
help the Straw Hats escape from here.
You guys probably knew that something
was up, but now we know the truth.
He saved the Sunny,
and he saved our lives.
And then, after we were
sent flying from the island,
Kuma paid Rayleigh a visit
and dropped another bombshell.
I don't have much time.
Not as myself.
The details are a little
sketchy, but evidently,
Kuma surrendered his body to the Navy.
They used him as an experiment and
replaced his body parts one by one.
By the time the War of
the Best rolled around,
his personality had been
completely erased. Wait!
He knew where he sent us, but he didn't
know what we'd do once we got there,
or that we would even make it back!
And you said his personality was taken
away, but he still protected the Sunny?
The guy who worked on him is
this dude named Dr. Vegapunk,
and Kuma must have made
a deal with him because
he programmed one final
mission into his brain.
Defend the Thousand Sunny
from any attackers until
the moment that a straw
hat returns to claim it.
So even though he's been reduced
to a living weapon with no memory,
he's been carrying out his own orders,
protecting our ship for the past
two years to fulfill his last wish.
But why?
He barely knew us.
I mean, why'd it matter
to him? I don't know.
Maybe it's because of Luffy.
You said Kuma was part of
the Revolutionary Army,
and Luffy's dad is the
leader of those guys, right?
I don't know much about my dad,
but it seems like that robot
bear dude was a good guy,
so he can't be too bad if they're friends.
Kuma.
The bottom line is,
our survival and all the things we
accomplished in the past two years,
we owe to him.
Whatever his reason was,
we should be grateful.
And we may never find out the truth,
because it's not like we can ask
him to explain himself anymore.
All we can do now is
honor his memory and know
that Bartholomew Kuma
was our greatest ally,
until he took his last breath as a human.
Unfortunately, we'll never be able to
thank him since he'll just be a weapon,
and likely our enemy
the next time we meet.
That's all I wanted to say.
Kind of a lot to work through
all at once, isn't it?
Someday, I hope we can at least
find out the rest of the story.
Oh, you're awake. Good. Have some lunch.
It's from Amazon Lily.
Oh, Amazon Lily.
The island with all the women.
Of course that's where he sent you.
Do you know where I was
these past two years?
Because I'm kind of thinking Kuma's
not such a good friend after all.
In fact, if he were here right now,
I'd like to kick his metal face in!
Now, now, Sanji, we've all
had our share of troubles.
Before I became a pop music
sensation, I was trapped in a cage.
Still, the only thing that matters
now is the voyage awaiting us.
Straight ahead!
Brother, look! It's them! I know!
Like you said, they're straight ahead.
You think I'm blind?
Looks like we'll be sailing
with the Straw Hats after all.
Wow, how far down are we?
I don't know, but it's
getting darker and darker.
We passed the photic zone,
and it looks like we're around
the bottom of the a-photic zone.
About a thousand meters, give or take.
Quiet and the sunny
itself feels oddly still.
It's almost like floating in the sky.
Hey look it's a whale.
It's just like the moon.
Nah it looks more like white beard.
Wait a sec what is that thing?
A fish.
No are you ready we only
get one shot at this?
Ready brother ready captain.
Before you say anything.
I know what you're thinking.
Just shoot them and they'll all drown.
They're wanted dead or alive after
all, so why not let them die?
Well, that wouldn't do it all, because
the Navy wouldn't know who killed them.
We have to deliver their heads
personally on a silver platter.
Then they will fear us.
The whole world will do our strength.
We'll take them out before
they suspect a thing.
My big smiling face is the last
thing they'll see before they die.
Hey, you guys, there's a ship looking
thing coming our way what you sure?
Why don't you come look for yourself?
It's a pirate ship!
They're ramming straight into us!
Go away you morons!
You're gonna make us all drown!
They're not trying to break our
ship, they're trying to board it!
Tumit? Who are they?
Keep it up, Seacow! Yeah!
You think they want to board the ship?
Seacow?
I know that noise from somewhere.
Good.
Is everybody ready?
Yeah!
Mama, it's me!
We've met before!
You're from the Arlong Pirates, right?
Nami!
I was at Arlong Park!
Hey, Luffy, doesn't that
thing look kind of familiar?
I don't know.
Go, go, pistol!
Let's pay our new friends
a visit, shall we?
Let's stay out of here!
There's no time to waste!
Follow my lead!
Fools!
They're completely dumbfounded!
If they're gonna sit there catching flies,
then we'll strike while the iron is hot!
We'll smite this entire crew, right now!
Come along, men!
We'll make the beggars for mercy!
What's wrong, Skull? Don't panic!
That's not good.
We have Captain Carable
on the ship back there.
Never!
Now, it's time for a little greeting.
Fire the Gatling gun, men!
Shower them in bullets!
I want every last one of them dead!
Send these Straw Hats to hell!
No! Wait!
You're not going to throw
me into the water, are you?
Please don't do that to me, my friend!
I'm begging you!
By the way, you're very good-looking!
I'm sure someone like you understands
the value of human life, right?
Emphasize!
The gods are watching!
You'll be judged for this!
Oh, make up your freaking mind already!
Weren't you just about to fire your Gatling
gun and blast to saw the kingdom come?
Anyway, tell me, I know you're the captain
of that ship, but what's your name?
That's Roro no Zoro!
Don't be ridiculous!
What in the world makes you
think I would be the captain?
I'm... Oh!
Those ruffians were keeping me as a...
a slave! That's it! Boy! Ooh!
Glad that's over!
Say, how's this?
Do you think I could stay on this nice
ship with you all for a little while?
Huh? Please? Wow.
I feel kind of sorry for this poor loser.
HE'S OBVIOUSLY LYING!
ARE YOU CRAZY?!
WHAT?!
SERIOUSLY?!
Hey, I have a question.
Where'd that giant sea cow
pulling your ship come from?
Hello?
Oh, my.
Who's this vixen?
I take it you're the famous cat burglar.
Watch it, pal!
Nobody's allowed to drool over our
beautiful navigator except for me!
Don't worry.
You're perfectly s -
Hey, it's getting really old!
Cut it out!
The sea cow? Who knows?
I just happened to catch it
out in the ocean somewhere.
When you're underwater,
having a sea monster pull your ship
is the mark of an experienced captain.
Huh?
Awesome!
Stop it, sea cow!
What's the problem? Oh, brother!
We're on our way to rescue you!
I'm gonna find a sea monster, too!
What crazy ideas are
you hatching now, Luffy?
We should try to rehabilitate him with
something a little less sexy. Hey, Nami,
the direction we're taking isn't exactly
the same way the Log Pose is pointing.
Oh, no problem.
The correct course is technically
southwest, so we're in the clear.
Yeah, but if we went in a straight line,
we could get there a whole lot faster,
couldn't we?
Well, if you go straight, you risk
getting swept away in a sea current.
And if that should happen, you might run
into an underwater mountain or a volcano,
see?
That's why.
Yikes!
I'm with you on this one.
Yeah, but I thought all the
currents here were dangerous.
It is the Grand Line, after all.
So are you saying that some
of them are actually stable?
Well, this one is.
Now you stay put. Hey!
It's gonna start getting
colder from here on out,
so make sure you put
on a coat or something.
You bring up a good point.
I'm already starting to
feel goosebumps on my skin.
Well, except for I...
You don't have any skin
because you're a skeleton.
Chopper, skull jokes are
the only thing I have.
Please don't take that away from me.
We're going somewhere
cold, not the deep sea.
Don't you guys know the
water's cold in the deep sea?
It's just like a bathtub.
Hot water rises and cold
sinks to the bottom.
Aha,
because heat rises and
there's not much sunlight,
so there's nothing to
heat the water down here.
The temperature's not the only thing
that's different at the bottom.
You're not still depressed, are you?
Once we move down, we'll find
something called deep currents.
You don't run into them terribly often,
but they're much larger
than the regular currents.
Also,
they're quite unique in that
their flow is completely
independent of what you
see closer to the surface.
Currents under the currents and
you even have a diagram, huh?
You sure do know a lot of stuff.
That's because I'm so old.
Not only that, but all currents
are connected to each other.
That doesn't mean they have
to flow in the same direction.
They flow east, west, up and down.
It's like a big long
dragon all tangled up.
The deep currents tend to travel
at a surprisingly slow pace.
After they reach the deep sea,
it takes approximately
2,000 years before they
finally make their way up
to the surface of the water.
That makes me feel young again, actually.
2,000?
Yes, 2,000.
And because of that,
there are countless tales about what
lurks within those deep, dark currents.
Monsters. Curses.
The Wrath of the Undead.
You mean the deep sea is haunted? What?
The sea is haunted? Help!
That sounds fun to me!
Calm down, guys.
I don't know anything about
the Wrath of the Undead,
or whatever you're freaking out about,
but I do know that we'll encounter
a downward-flowing current soon.
Once we do, we should be able to
ride it down into the deep sea.
She said something about deep
sea currents, I don't know.
You morons can at least
pretend like you understand me.
Nami, I see it.
Really?
Check it out!
Amazing.
This one's called the downward plume.
It's almost like a giant waterfall.
Except underwater!
It's going so fast!
The sea is like falling into the sea,
which doesn't make sense, but I like it!
Mother Nature, you're one crazy lady!
What a spectacular sight!
And from the looks of it, I'd
say the stream runs barely deep.
I've heard stories about these currents,
but they did not do them justice.
It's crazy dark down there!
The floor so far, you can't even see it!
We're dead!
At this speed, we're gonna get
pile-driven straight down to the bottom!
You sure it's safe if we
just go with the flow?
If you're worried about
the ship, don't be.
Sunny was built from
the treasure tree, Adam.
It's as tough as they come.
Okay!
Let's go!
Oh?
Is that crap?
So it really does live down here.
It's no legend.
Please listen to me, Straw Hats.
We have to turn back.
We're gonna die. Oh, yeah.
I forgot you were here.
There's a sea monster.
It's the Kraken.
A legendary giant octopus monster.
He made fish food out of those ships.
They left for the new world.
And never made it.
Turn around, please.
I'm not ready to die.
I beg you.
Just wait around for a couple days.
And it'll probably go away.
Shut up for a sec.
I just had a perfect idea.
Guys.
We just have to capture it.
Huh?
Have you lost your mind, Loopy?
If we catch it, we can teach
it how to pull the ship.
Like hell we can.
I tell you, look at it, but
it's so ridiculously huge.
I don't know how in the world
you can miss a damn thing.
Yeah, I gotta get it, babe.
I can't die.
It must have been here for centuries.
The Kraken shows have been
missed from all over the world.
It's one of the most terrible
monsters that ever lived.